Guide to the Records of the Student Senators Council RG.44.0.1
New York University Archives
- Series VIII: Membership, 1975-2018; 15.75 Linear Feet in 36 manuscript boxes
  - Availability Forms, 1995-1996 (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - Committee Preference Forms SSC, 1995-1996 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - Committee Preference & Description (Student Body Alternates), 1995-1996 (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - Committee Preference Forms, UCSL, 1995-1996 (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Council - Personal Information Sheets, 1995-1996 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Guest Attendance List, 1995-1996 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Membership Lists, 1995-1996 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Student Senators-at-Large 1996-1997, 1995-1996 (Box 135, Folder 4-5)
  - Student Senators-at-Large Current, 1995-1996 (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - Alternate Senators, 1996-1997 (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Attendance Lists, 1996-1997 (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - Availability Forms, 1996-1997 (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - Committee Chairs, 1996-1997 (Box 135, Folder 10)
  - Committee Preference and Description Student Body & Alternatives, 1996-1997 (Box 135, Folder 11)
  - Committee Preference Forms, SSC, 1996-1997 (Box 135, Folder 12)
  - Committee Preference Forms, UCSL, 1996-1997 (Box 135, Folder 13)
  - Guest Attendance List, 1996-1997 (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Membership Faculty Council (FC) & SSC, 1996-1997 (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Membership Lists, 1996-1997 (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Student Senators-at-Large: 1997-1998, 1996-1997 (Box 136, Folder 4-5)
  - Student Senators at Large Applications, 1996-1997 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Student Senators-at-Large: Current, 1996-1997 (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Alternate Senators, 1997-1998 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Attendance Lists, 1997-1998 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Availability Forms, 1997-1998 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Committee Preference Forms SSC, 1997-1998 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Committee Preference Forms UCSL, 1997-1998 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Flier Distribution List (Deans), 1997-1998 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - Guest Attendance Lists, 1997-1998 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Membership Lists, 1997-2000 (Box 137, Folder 9-10)
  - Program Board, 1997-1998 (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - Student Senators-at-Large: 1998-1999, 1997-1998 (Box 137, Folder 12, Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Student Senators-at-Large: Current, 1997-1998 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Alternate Senators (at-Large), 1998-1999 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Attendance Lists, 1998-1999 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Availability Forms, 1998-1999 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Committee Preference & Description (Student Body/Alternates), 1998-1999 (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Committee Preference Forms (SSC), 1998-1999 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Committee Preference Forms (UCSL), 1998-1999 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Guest Attendance Lists, 1998-1999 (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - Membership Lists and Information, 1998-1999 (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - Student Senators-at-Large: 1999-2000, 1998-1999 (Box 138, Folder 11, Box 139, Folder 1-2)
  - Student Senators-at-Large: Current, 1998-1999 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Attendance Lists, 1999-2000 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Availability Forms, 1999-2000 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Committee Chairs, 1999-2000 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Committee Preference Forms (SSC), 1999-2000 (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Committee Preference Forms (UCSL), 1999-2000 (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Guest Attendance Lists, 1999-2000 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Membership Lists, 1999-2000 (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - Student Senators-at-Large: 2000-2001, 1999-2000 (Box 140, Folder 1-2)
  - Senators-at-Large, Current, 1999-2000 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Attendance Lists, 2000-2001 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Availability Forms, 2000-2001 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Committee Preference and Description (Student Body/Alternates), 2000-2001 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Committee Preference Forms, 2000-2001 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - Committee Preference Forms UCSL, 2000-2001 (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - Election of Officers, 2000-2001 (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - Membership Lists, 2000-2001 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Student Senators-at-Large, 2000-2001 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Student Senators-at-Large: 2001-2002, 2000-2001 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Student Senators-at-Large: Current, 2000-2001 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Attendance Lists, 2001-2002 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Availability Forms, 2001-2002 (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - Censure (RESTRICTED), 2001-2002 (Box 159, Folder 13)
  - Committee Chairs, 2001-2002 (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - Committee Preference Forms, SSC, 2001-2002 (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - Committee Preference Forms, UCSL, 2001-2002 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Guest Attendance List, 2001-2002 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Membership Lists, 2001-2003 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Membership Lists and Information, 2001-2002 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Student Senators-at-Large: 2002-2003, 2001-2002 (Box 142, Folder 5-7)
  - Attendance List, 2002-2003 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Availability Forms, 2002-2003 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Censure (RESTRICTED), 2001-2002 (Box 159, Folder 14)
  - Committee Chairs, 2002-2003 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Committee Preference and Description (Student Body/Alternates), 2002-2003 (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Committee Preference Forms, SSC, 2002-2003 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Committee Preference Forms, UCSL, 2002-2003 (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Coordinated Election Period, 2002-2003 (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Guest Attendance Lists, 2002-2003 (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - Memberships Lists and Information, 2002-2003 (Box 143, Folder 9-10)
  - Recommendations for Student Senators-at-Large, 2002-2003 (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - Student Senators-at-Large 2003-2004, 2002-2003 (Box 144, Folder 1-4)
  - Student Senators-at-Large: Current, 2002-2003 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Alternate Senators, 2003-2004 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Attendance List, 2003-2004 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Availability Forms, 2003-2004 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Censure, 2003-2004 (Box 159, Folder 15)
  - Committee Preference Forms SSC, 2003-2004 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Committee Preference Forms UCSL, 2003-2004 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Guest Attendance Lists, 2003-2004 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Membership Lists and Information, 2003-2004 (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - Student Senators-at-Large: 2004-2005, 2003-2004 (Box 145, Folder 8-9)
  - Student Senators-at-Large: Current, 2003-2004 (Box 145, Folder 10)
  - Attendance List, 2004-2005 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Availability Forms, 2004-2005 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Committee Preference Forms SSC, 2004-2005 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Committee Preference Forms UCSL, 2004-2005 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - Guest Attendance Lists, 2004-2005 (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - Membership Lists, 2004-2008 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Membership Lists and Information, 2004-2005 (Box 146, Folder 7-8)
  - Student Senators-at-Large, 2005-2006, 2004-2005 (Box 146, Folder 9)
  - Student Senators-at-Large, Current, 2004-2005 (Box 146, Folder 10)
  - Webpage, 2004-2005 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Attendance List, 2005-2006 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Availability Forms, 2005-2006 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Committee Chairs, 2005-2006 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Committee Preference Forms, SSC, 2005-2006 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - Committee Preference Forms, UCSL, 2005-2006 (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - Guest Attendance Lists, 2005-2006 (Box 147, Folder 7)
  - Label List, 2005-2006 (Box 147, Folder 8)
  - Membership Lists and Information, 2005-2006 (Box 147, Folder 9)
  - Student Affairs Counterparts, 2005-2006 (Box 147, Folder 10)
  - Student Senators-at-Large: 2006-2007, 2005-2006 (Box 147, Folder 11-13, Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Student Senators-at-Large Current, 2005-2006 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - 2006-2007 Election Result Forms (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Attendance List, 2006-2007 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Availability Info, 2006-2007 (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - Committee Chairs, 2006-2007 (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - Committee Preference Forms SSC, 2006-2007 (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Committee Preference Forms UCSL, 2006-2007 (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - Enclosures for Senators-at-Large, Alts, and Rejects, 2006-2007 (Box 148, Folder 9)
  - Guest Attendance List, 2006-2007 (Box 148, Folder 10)
  - Membership Lists and Information, 2006-2007 (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - Preference (SSC), 2006-2007 (Box 148, Folder 12)
  - Preference (UCSL), 2006-2007 (Box 148, Folder 13)
  - Student Body Preference/Availability (Alternates), 2006-2007 (Box 148, Folder 14)
  - Senators-at-Large for 2007-2008, 2006-2007 (Box 148, Folder 15, Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Student Senators-at-Large: Current, 2006-2007 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Attendance List, 2007-2008 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Committee Chairs, 2007-2008 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Guest Attendance, 2007-2008 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Membership Lists and Information, 2007-2008 (Box 149, Folder 6-7)
  - Senators-at-Large, 2007-2008 (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Student Council Results, 2007-2008 (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - Student Senators-at-Large: Current, 2007-2008 (Box 149, Folder 10)
  - Student Senators-at-Large Next Year, 2007-2008 (Box 150, Folder 1-3)
  - Composition of Senate Committees for Academic Year 2008-2009 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Student Activity Report, 2008 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Student Government at New York University Flyer, 2008 (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Attendance List, 2008-2009 (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - Availability Forms, 2008-2009 (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - Committee Preference Forms SSC, 2008-2009 (Box 150, Folder 9)
  - Committee Preference Forms UCSL, 2008-2009 (Box 150, Folder 10)
  - Guest Attendance Lists, 2008-2009 (Box 150, Folder 11)
  - Membership Lists and Information, 2008-2009 (Box 150, Folder 12)
  - Student Senators-at-Large: Current, 2008-2009 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Student Senators-at-Large: Next Year's Applicants, 2008-2009 (Box 151, Folder 2-3)
  - New York University Faculty Handbook, 2009 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - 2014-2015 Senator at-Large Elections (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Council Candidates, 2014-2015 (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - University Committee on Student Life Committee Assignments, 2014-2015 (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Student Senators Council - Senators-at-Large Selection Binder, 2016-2017 (Box 151, Folder 8-9)
  - Senators-at-Large Elections 2017-2018 - Second Round Vote (Box 152, Folder 1)
- Series IX: Student Resources, 1977-2015; 3.06 Linear Feet in 7 manuscript boxes
  Series IX: Student Resources documents the ways in which the Student Senators Council assisted New York University students, particularly new members to the community, by producing and providing educational materials that were distributed amongst the student body. The Student Senators Council produced and circulated student handbooks, welcome packets with general information about New York City, guides to the University services, campus information, and pamphlets explaining the organization and function of the SSC.
  - NYU Law School Directory, 1977-1978 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Student Organization (GSO) Graduate Tidings, 1978-1979 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Pre Law Journal, 1978-1979 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Public Affairs: Athletics Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Senate Diagram, 1979-1980 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Class Song, Class of 1900, 1980-1981 (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - Dance Marathon, 1980-1981 (Box 152, Folder 8)
  - Student Handbook, 1980-1981 (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - Orientation, 1981-1982 (Box 152, Folder 10)
  - Student Handbook, 1981-1982 (Box 152, Folder 11)
  - New York University Telephone Directory, 1982 (Box 152, Folder 12)
  - All-University Student Council Day, 1982-1983 (Box 152, Folder 13)
  - Freshman Orientation, 1982-1983 (Box 152, Folder 14)
  - Harvard Summer Internship, 1982-1983 (Box 152, Folder 15)
  - Student Handbook, 1982-1983 (Box 152, Folder 16)
  - NYU Medical Center Telephone Directory, 1983 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Freshman Orientation & Convocation, 1983-1984 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - New York University Fact Sheet, 1983-1984 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Student Handbook, 1983-1984 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Folders: Free Distribution, 1984-1985 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Orientation Materials 1984, 1984-1985 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Students' Guide to NYU 84-85, 1984-1985 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - University Student Directory, 1984-1985 (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Loeb Student Center - Manual of Policies and Procedures, 1985 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Student Activities Annex Brochures, 1985 (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - New York University Telephone Directory, 1985 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - New York University Bulletin - School of Medicine, 1985-1987 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Student Activities - School Wide, 1985-1986 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - New York University Fact Sheet, 1986-1988 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - New York University Catering Services, 1987 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - NYU Phones, 1988 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Senate Materials, Publications, 1988-1989 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - New York University Housing and Residence Life, 1989 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - Summer in New York City at New York University, 1989 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - The Student's Guide to NYU, 1989-1992 (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - New York University Revised Fall 1990 Class Schedule (Box 154, Folder 11)
  - New York University Student Guide to Cross-School Advisement & Registration, 1990-1991 (Box 154, Folder 12)
  - Orientation Materials (Stud. Aff.), 1990-1991 (Box 154, Folder 13)
  - Telephone Directory, 1990-1991 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter, 1993-1994 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Student Guide to NYU, 1993-1994 (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Resource Guide to Students, 1995-1996 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - All University Orientation, 1996 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Original Handbook, 1996 (Box 155, Folder 6-7)
  - 1997 Directory of Minority Doctoral Recipeints and Candidates in New York State (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - Student Government Handbook, 1997 (Box 155, Folder 9-10, Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Student Guide to NYU, 1997-1998 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Student Government Handbook, 1998 (Box 156, Folder 3-5)
  - Originals for Student Gov Handbook, 1999 (Box 156, Folder 6-7)
  - Resource Guide to Students, 1999-2000 (Box 156, Folder 8)
  - All-University Undergraduate Advertisement Guide, 2000-2001 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Office of Student Activities, 2000-2001 (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Student Government Handbook, 2000-2001 (Box 157, Folder 3-4)
  - Student Guide to NYU, 2000-2002 (Box 157, Folder 5-6)
  - Orientation, 2003-2004 (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - Student Guide to NYU, 2003-2004 (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - The Campaign for NYU Booklet, 2004-2005 (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - Handbook (Originals), 2004-2005 (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Office of Student Activities, 2004-2005 (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - Student Affairs, 2004-2005 (Box 158, Folder 3-4)
  - Student Guide to NYU, 2004-2005 (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Handbook (Originals), 2005-2006 (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - New York University, Academic Year 2006-2007 Magnet (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - NYU Abu Dhabi - Student Constitution, 2011-2012 (Box 158, Folder 8)
  - 2014 Senator Binder, 2013-2014 (Box 158, Folder 9)
  - 2015 Senator Binder, 2014-2015 (Box 158, Folder 10)
- Series X: Board of Trustees, 1981-1990; 0.22 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box
  In the 1980s, the Student Senators Council worked with New York University's Board of Trustees to establish a solid foundation for the SSC's future growth. Series X contains memorandum, transcript of speeches given by members of the SSC/UCSL to the Board of Trustees, and dinner invitations found within this series.
  Board of Trustees records are closed for 35 years from the date of creation. Box 159 contains restricted materials.
  - Board of Trustees Dinner, 1981-1982 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees Presentation, 1981-1982 (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees Dinner, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees Presentation, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees, 1989-1990 (Box 159, Folder 5)